[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
Thank you.
This won't work.
I'm breaking up with you.
What?
Why? At least give me a reason.
You can't just break up with me.
I want to.
What part of that don't you understand?
Please don't do this to me again.
Please.
Wait.
You're doing well.
You can do this.
You're just like me.
Ke!
Are you busy?
Why?
So I found this cafe near Kalix's office.
Come on. Come with me.
Ugh, you just want company
while you wait for Kalix.
Come on, please?
Wait, are you even
allowed to drink coffee?
It's decaf. Besides, it's my treat.
Okay.
Oh, so now you're in when it's free?
All right, all right, I'll get ready.
See you in a bit.
- Okay. I love you.
- Bye.
Hm. You've really gone
full matcha mode, huh.
It's been ages since
you've had coffee, right?
And it looks like I'll still
be avoiding coffee for a while.
And you,
you shouldn't be having coffee
too often either, even if it's decaf.
Gotta take care of the baby.
Right, baby? Mommy
shouldn't be so stubborn.
Hey, I just ordered
strawberry milk instead, okay.
Geez.
Oh, by the way!
Have you heard about Amethyst?
The attempted murder?
I really wish that
case would move faster.
So many people are waiting on it.
Speaking of.
Oh, it's my baby.
That governor's probably gonna win again.
I'm sure the prosecutor
in charge already got paid off.
You know how dirty the system
is these days, it's all about money now.
I still hold out hope that there
are still some decent people out there.
I hope they haven't been
paid off or blinded by money yet.
It's so hard to trust anyone these days.
Look at his kid. It took so long
to get him locked up,
even though there's so much
he still needs to answer for.
Hi, Love.
- Hey, Love! How are you?
- Hi.
Have you guys had lunch yet?
Join us for lunch. Come on.
Thank you, but I'll just take it to go.
I'm on a working lunch break.
I'm meeting Prosecutor Lopez
for the Villaflor case. So, excuse me.
Ah, Shan Lopez.
So he's the prosecutor.
Villaflor's gonna get off scot-free.
It's actually gonna be the second Villaflor
that he will be sending
to jail if he wins the case.
What do you mean?
That he's the prosecutor
who got Miguel in jail.
He got the first prosecutor suspended,
and he also replaced them.
So, let's just say that he
won the case without mercy.
Love, come on.
Come on. Stop defending Fiscal Lopez.
She has a reason
to be mad at him, remember?
Besides, you and Sunday
aren't even close, right?
We're actually close.
I'm not interested in him anymore, okay?
Yeah, that's over. I'm done with that.
Yeah, it's over.
It's fine now.
So he really did do it.
Damn it.
Where are you even looking?
Why'd you just suddenly
back straight out like that?
I was happy back then.
Especially when I was young.
Just playing around.
Laughing. Free.
Because I was always with Luna back then.
I can jump farther than you.
No, mine's farther. Look.
Oh no, are you okay?
- Yes. I'm okay.
- Are you crying?
It doesn't even hurt; why would I cry?
Baby!
What happened?
Are you okay?
Does it hurt?
No, mom. I'm not gonna cry
because it doesn't hurt.
Baby, it's okay. It's okay to cry, okay?
If it hurts, just cry.
Mommy is here.
Mommy is always here, okay?
If you cry, I'll cry with you
so we're the same.
Having Luna,
I knew I always had
someone in my corner.
Ke! Do Teacher Sandra.
Luna, Kierra! Stop being so annoying.
You're so loud, Kierra.
I'm gonna tell the teacher on you.
You're so gonna get it.
Huh! Why only me?
Just ignore Harold,
he's just seeking attention.
Yeah, we're not even doing anything to him.
But he's always mean to me.
The other day,
he even made fun of my hair.
It's because he's got
a crush on you, that's why.
He just wants your attention.
That's fine.
Oh...
So you're supposed
to be mean to your crush?
Yeah, seriously, I already ate.
Have you eaten?
I miss you.
All right, see you next week.
Okay, I love you.
When's it gonna be my turn?
But I was jealous.
I wanted to be in love like that.
What are we gonna watch?
I want a romantic comedy.
Huh? Romantic comedy?
- Didn't we just watch one last week?
- Yeah, we did.
I just really want
to feel the butterflies, mommy.
Butterflies? Why?
Is someone at school
making you feel giddy?
Is someone courting you, sweetie?
Introduce him to me. Bring him here.
- Daddy, no-
- Just an interview.
It's just gonna be an interview.
There's no one, that's
why I want to feel giddy.
Besides, I don't have a crush
on anyone there. None of them are my type.
This daughter of mine
is really something else, huh.
Well, what do you want?
I want what you and daddy have.
I want that love that
you guys have for each other.
Someday you will find that someone.
I can't wait for that someday to come.
How are you feeling, Kierra?
It's been months since your last visit.
I'm okay.
Really? You look tired.
Are you able to sleep?
Yes.
Sometimes I wake up at night.
I keep
having these
dreams...
memories?
Dreams?
What dreams?
I’m...
in a parking lot.
Then-
Sorry.
I don't want to talk about it anymore.
Um...
I just want to forget it.
I see.
It's okay. You don't
have to force yourself.
What are you feeling right now?
I feel...
I feel suffocated.
When I'm at home-
it's like I can't breathe.
And when I'm outside,
I feel anxious.
I'm-
I'm afraid I might...
I might bump into him.
I feel like I'm...
I'm in a...
I feel like I'm trapped in two places.
I don't know where I can hide.
So right now, what do you want to do?
I want to breathe.
Let it out.
Put those in the bag there.
- Uncle! Auntie!
- Hi!
Hello.
Daddy.
Oh my god, Auntie.
Is this our food?
Of course.
This is gonna be good for a week.
Glad you guys stopped by.
School's about to start. So you'd better
stock up before you guys get busy again.
Yeah.
How are you?
Looks like you didn't
get much sleep last night.
Mhmm.
Um-
We just watched too many movies.
Are you sure?
Because if you're having
trouble sleeping again,
we can visit your doctor.
No, I'm really okay.
Actually, I just came from therapy earlier.
And I think we're making good progress.
Slowly but surely, I'll be okay too.
That's good to hear, sweetie.
It really is better
when the sessions are regular.
So, just keep it up, okay.
Mhmm.
And don't worry, Uncle, Auntie, Kierra's
got a personal caregiver right here.
All set. And free, too.
Luna, thank you. You really are an angel.
Come.
Eat first before you guys leave.
Come on, let's go.
- Come on now.
- I'm hungry.
Wow.
This looks so good.
Ke! Via and I are still out,
we'll be home late.
Is that so? Okay,
take care, you guys.
Is she sure? Do you want us
to go check on her?
Ke, are you okay?
Do you want me to
come home now? You want company?
Ah, I'm fine here. Enjoy yourselves.
Okay. Bye-bye.
Okay, bye.
Let's eat.
You've got some nerve.
Fuck. You're such a flirt.
You're a slut!
Ke! How are you?
Hi, Ke!
We're heading home soon.
Have you had dinner yet?
Not yet.
But I'm eating out.
Should we go see her?
Ke, where are you? We'll come meet you.
No, no need.
I'm fine, Luna.
But Ke, you don't like eating out alone.
I'm okay.
It's okay. I'm at Claremont Hotel.
The last time I went
here, I was with him.
And he hates it here.
He said the service was shitty,
the food tastes awful,
so he said he's never coming back.
So I'm sure I won't run into him.
So don't worry, okay?
I'll head home right after I eat.
Okay, all right. Just message us, okay?
We'll come get you right away.
We're here for you, Ke.
Thank you, Luna, Via.
Fuck.
The food here is so bad.
Excuse me!
Excuse me, Miss?
Is something wrong?
Who are you?
Are you okay?
Did someone ditch you?
Why are you crying?
That's quite a long name.
Can I sit here?
Why ask when you're already seated?
I got ditched, too.
I'm not asking.
Well, aren't you grouchy?
But I like this better than
what was on your face earlier.
I just noticed.
Were you watching me?
No.
You just caught my attention.
Because earlier you seemed scared.
Did you get into a fight?
Is there someone bothering you?
Is he here?
You just don't know,
I'm really good at fighting.
He's not here.
But there's really someone.
I have an idea.
I know what will make you happy.
Please tell me ice cream is
your favorite comfort food.
I mean, if I'm wrong
I'd feel guilty about it.
Yeah, ice cream, but you
got the wrong flavor.
I like chocolate, not vanilla.
But on some occasions,
I like strawberry.
But your personality is
more of a dark chocolate.
Is guessing ice cream flavors based on
people's personalities your hobby?
Do they pay you for that?
Why?
Are you willing to pay me?
Don't worry, it's free.
And next time you can be
the one to treat me to ice cream.
There won't be a next time.
There will be.
Trust me.
So, how are you getting home?
I mean, I'd like to offer to bring
you home, but since I'm a stranger,
you might just be scared.
If you want, I can book you a ride.
Here's my number.
Call me if anything happens.
Is this how you get girls?
It's pretty lame.
Did you just assume that I like you?
Oh.
Are you projecting it onto me?
So I'm your type, huh?
Do you wanna sleep with me?
Sex won't solve any
of your problems, woman.
I'm not asking you to solve it, and
I'm not asking you to have sex.
Okay.
I have a room upstairs.
You can order anything, and then,
let's take it from there.
Ciandrei.
Ciandrei Kyle is my name.
But you can call me Shan.
You're not taken, right?
'Cause I hate cheaters.
How about you?
Nope.
Never.
So, what do you want?
Do you wanna order anything?
They have some dessert,
they have some shakes.
They have bingsu.
Let's get that.
So, why are you here?
Why did you come with me?
Why did you even trust me?
I don't.
You've got some nerve
thinking I trust you.
I'll turn your question back to you.
Why did you bring me here?
Do you trust me?
What if I do something to you?
Scary.
Really.
What if I kiss you?
You won't.
Why?
How are you so sure?
What if...
What if we play truth or dare?
Are you that bored?
Fine. All right, sure.
We'll take turns, but I go first.
Tell me the truth.
What is your name?
Is that your question?
Shouldn't you have asked
me truth or dare first?
Fine.
Truth or dare?
Dare.
Kiss me.
You can't do it?
Okay. It's either you kiss me
or you finish the bingsu
and tell me your name.
Hello!
Hi, yes. Good morning.
Can I order a breakfast for one?
Sure ma’am, what room number?
Hello?
Uhm... Yes.
Can you charge it to Room 237?
- Okay, ma'am.
- Yes, thank you.
You’re welcome.
Thanks for last night.
You made me feel less alone.
But I hope I don't see you again.
Ke, where are you? Please answer.
Ke?
And why are you just getting home now?
You scared me.
Ke! Do you know how
worried I was for you?
I sent you a ton of messages;
I called you a lot of times.
Do you know how close I was to just-
My phone died last night.
Wait. What's that?
- Huh?
- Fuck! What is that?
Hey, hey. It's nothing.
It's not a bruise. Luna, I'm fine.
- What do you mean it's not a bruise?
- It's not a bruise.
It's nothing.
Sit down.
Sit.
If that's not a bruise-
Let me sleep first.
Wait.
Do you have a boyfriend?
No.
You don't have a boyfriend?
- Nothing.
- But what is that?
- It's just nothing.
- Fuck buddy?
One night stand?
What do you mean nothing?
It was just a one-night stand,
and it won't happen again.
That wasn't me last night.
That wasn't you last night?
Were you possessed, Ke?
What's going on?
I don't know, but
at least she was free.
I know I used someone to forget.
I know it's wrong, so don't
lecture me anymore, please.
All right. Go get some rest.
Get some rest, first day of school
starts tomorrow for us.
Are you ready?
We're in our third year now.
Just, let's not talk about it anymore.
Okay?
Because I already regret last night.
And I won't see that guy again anyway.
You'll be okay, Kierra.
You'll be safe.
Don't worry.
Ready?
We're in third year now.
Let's go.
Via!
Luna, Ke.
My Via.
How are you?
Hi, guys!
Hey, Luna, is the party still on later?
Yes. Of course, the party's
still happening later.
All right. See you later, okay?
Okay, see you!
What party?
Well, it's the first day
of our block today, right?
So there's a party.
But it's okay if you don't come.
It's okay.
No, I'm coming.
Can you handle it? You sure?
Better than being cooped up
in my room anyway.
I'll go too.
Yay! Okay, perfect, the
three of us are complete.
Okay...
Let's drink!
Are you okay?
Are you sure you can handle this?
I'm okay.
Don't worry, we won't leave you.
Thank you, Luna. Thank you, Via.
Hey!
Hello.
Come here!
Come on, let's go.
Come on, take a shot!
Shots!
We're third years now!
- Cheers!
Okay!
Excuse me.
Come on! Cheers!
You sure? Can you handle more?
Take it slow, okay?
Yes.
Wait, where's Luna?
She went to the bathroom earlier,
but that was a while ago though.
Should we check on her?
Let's go.
I’ll go with you.
That way-
Hey, why are you guys
over there? Come on, let's dance.
It's fine, I'll go.
All right then.
- Let's go.
- Okay, okay.
- You sure?
- Yes, go ahead.
What the fuck...
Hi, miss.
Woah. Relax.
I just wanna know your name.
Please-
Get in the fucking car.
Let go, man.
Okay, okay.
Excuse me.
Whatever you're running from,
it'll all come back when you wake up.
Who are you?
Pain.
Trauma.
Memories.
It won't go away that easily.
Stop, stop...
Stop...
Let's not do this again.
It's not good for you.
I want to go to college already.
What do you mean?
We just started high school.
I'm just looking forward to that freedom.
Freedom.
- Three!
- You can really hold your liquor!
- Four!
- Five!
- Six!
- Seven!
- Eight!
Can we just be together?
Just us?
Come on, let's make it official already.
Come on.
I already told you before...
I'm not the type of guy who commits.
And how about now, Shan?
How are you feeling?
Hey, by the way...
Have you been sleeping lately?
Ke!
Sorry-
- Is he bothering you?
- No.